react.js a half-baked functional ui library created at facebook that's used
react.js 一个在 facebook 创建的半生不熟的功能性 ui库，已
by millions of developers because it has a cool name and logo it was invented by
被数百万开发人员使用，因为它有一个很酷的名称和徽标，它是由
mark zuckerberg in 2013. and that was a big mistake
马克·扎克伯格在 2013 年发明的。这是一个很大的错误
and it was my mistake and i'm sorry react is simple it's just javascript bro
，这是我的错误，我 对不起，react 很简单，它只是 javascript 兄弟
and that's why it gives you dozens of weird ways to solve the same problems
，这就是为什么它为您提供了许多奇怪的方法来解决相同的问题，
like functional and class-based components hooks forward ref higher
例如功能和基于类的组件挂钩转发 ref
order components mix-ins render props suspense and so on it's credited as the
高阶组件混合组件渲染道具悬念等等它被认为是
first declarative ui library even though it took most of those ideas from
第一个声明性 ui 库，尽管它采用了
angularjs its killer feature though is the fact that you can write pure
angularjs 中的大部分想法，但它的杀手级特性是你可以编写纯
functional code that is until you want to do anything useful in which case
函数式代码，直到你想做任何有用的事情，在这种情况下
you'll need to write imper functions with state and effects the beauty of
你需要编写带有状态的不正确函数 和效果这种方法的美妙之
this approach is that it makes simple things like reactive state much more
处在于它使像反应状态这样简单的事情
complicated than they need to be and that's what makes us feel like real
比它们需要的复杂得多，这就是让我们感觉像真正的
developers use effect is especially fun and was originally going to be called
开发人员使用效果 i 特别有趣，最初被称为
use foot gun because it's a great way to introduce infinite loops performance
使用脚枪，因为它是引入无限循环性能
issues and bugs that you'll never be able to figure out not to worry though
问题和错误的
react is always evolving with revolutionary new features to monkey
好方法
patch all the weirdness nobody saw coming on the previous release now even
修补以前版本中没有人看到的所有奇怪之处，
though it has an extremely high learning curve react is a library and not a
即使它具有极高的学习曲线，react 是一个库而不是
framework and that means to build something cool you'll need to find and
框架，这意味着要构建一些很酷的东西，你需要找到并
install hundreds of different packages most of which were built by teenagers
安装数百个不同的包 它是由几年前停止维护它们的青少年构建的，
who stopped maintaining them years ago when they went off to college to learn a
当时他们上大学学习
real language like c to get started create a new react app then open up
像 c 这样的真正语言开始创建一个新的 react 应用程序然后打开
google to enter the gates of tutorial hell notice how we start in strict mode
谷歌进入教程地狱注意我们如何在严格模式下开始
that's used to hide baggage from previous versions of the framework i
用于隐藏以前版本框架的包袱我的
mean library now in the code we pretend we're doing functional programming by
意思是现在在代码中的库我们假装我们正在通过
writing our components as functions classes are also possible but they are
编写我们的组件进行函数式编程 nts 作为函数类也是可能的，但它们
literally the double instead we use these hooks everywhere that do the same
实际上是双重的，而不是我们在任何地方都使用这些钩子，它们
classes do in a more magical hipstery way templating is handled in
以更神奇的时髦方式执行相同的狗屎类，模板在 jsx 中处理，
jsx it's a non-standard way to write html which allows you to represent the
这是编写 html 的非标准方式，它允许你
ui entirely in non-portable callback hell now we can all agree to hate css
完全在不可移植的回调地狱中代表 ui 现在我们都可以同意讨厌 css
but react will make you hate it even more when you try to style something on
但是当您尝试自己设置样式时，react 会让您更加讨厌它，
your own luckily there are hundreds of css and js libraries working on this
幸运的是，有数百个css 和 js 库正在解决这个
problem as we speak the extra complexity is worth it though because react is
问题，因为 我们说额外的复杂性是值得的，因为
blazingly fast assuming you implemented all the weird tricks flawlessly life is
假设你完美地实施了所有奇怪的技巧，反应速度非常快，生活就是
about suffering it's not supposed to be fun like spelt or fast like solid or
关于痛苦它不应该像拼写那样有趣或像固体一样快速或
reliable like angular or all of the above like view the only thing that
像角度那样可靠或像以上所有一样查看 唯一
matters is react is the most popular and that makes it undeniably the best just
重要的是 react 是最受欢迎的，这无疑使它成为最好的，
like microsoft makes the best operating system and mcdonald's makes the best
就像 microsoft 制造最好的操作系统而 mcdonald 制造最好的
food this has been me destroying my reputation with the react community in
foo  d 这让我在 100 秒内毁掉了我在 react 社区的声誉 react 在
100 seconds react has been the most influential library in front of web
development for the last decade nothing's perfect but it got to where it
过去十年中一直是 Web 开发领域最有影响
is today because it does a lot of things right and for that it deserves our
力的库 因为它值得我们
respect thanks for watching and i will see you in the next one
尊重感谢观看，我会在下一个看到你